Go on a date already
已经去约会了
Hurry up and go on a date
快点去约会吧
Can't wait anymore
不能再等了
Zheng Dedong and Weng Fanxi successfully matched
Zheng Dedong and Weng Fanxi successfully matched
It's truly wonderful
真是美妙极了
Actually, I really want
其实我真的很想要
to get in touch with Hu Wei again
再次联系胡伟
After going back, it's a whole different situation
回去之后，情况就完全不同了
I live in Singapore, you know
我住在新加坡，你知道的
We're still a bit too far apart
我们的距离还是有点远
Without these
没有这些
It's impossible to connect with you
无法与你联系
Come and pack your luggage quickly
快来收拾行李吧
Pack
盒
I'm leaving this place, Jiang Shangru.
我要离开这里了，姜尚如。
Let's meet often from now on.
从现在开始我们经常见面吧。
Do you feel sad?
你感到悲伤吗？
A little.
一点。
I think it's more like reluctance.
我觉得这更像是一种不情愿。
I feel reluctant to leave.
我有一种舍不得离开的感觉。
Because I really like everyone here.
因为我真的很喜欢这里的每个人。
I love the feeling of being together with everyone, you know?
我喜欢和大家在一起的感觉，你知道吗？
Now that I'm leaving, time seems to be passing faster.
现在我要走了，时间似乎过得更快了。
Tianyin has arrived
天音已到
Fellow islanders
岛民们
Today is our twelfth day on Tianping Island
今天是我们在天平岛的第十二天
The story of Tianping Island is coming to an end
天平岛的故事即将结束
All islanders please proceed to the public chat area
所有岛民请前往公共聊天区
Let's begin Tianping Island's final day together
一起开始天平岛的最后一天吧
I think the sky knows we're leaving
我想天空知道我们要离开
It's crying
它在哭
It's in a bad mood
心情不好
Normally at this time
通常这个时候
the sun would be shining directly on our faces
阳光会直接照在我们的脸上
and darkening our skin
并使我们的皮肤变黑
Your outfits match so well today
你今天的衣服很搭配
I'll wear khaki this afternoon
今天下午我会穿卡其色
a full suit
全套西装
Xiao Enya will wear black
小恩雅将穿黑色
Okay
好的
Perfect
完美的
There are decorations today
今天有装饰品
That's thoughtful
这很周到
Give me a hand
帮我一下
Little flower
小花
I ate too much instant noodles yesterday.
我昨天吃太多方便面了。
Me too.
我也是。
I'm guilty.
我有罪。
I like your perfume.
我喜欢你的香水。
Over there.
在那边。
Let's go together then.
那我们一起去吧。
Okay.
好的。
You sit here.
你坐在这里。
You sit over there.
你坐那边。
What is this, cowboy triple seating?
这是什么，牛仔三人座？
The three of us sitting together like cowboys.
我们三个像牛仔一样坐在一起。
Let's play a matching game.
我们来玩一个配对游戏吧。
We're leaving first.
我们先走了。
Today,
今天，
we'll begin the lost time retrieval session.
我们将开始损失时间检索会话。
In parallel universes,
在平行宇宙中，
there are fourteen timelines with different origins,
有十四条不同起源的时间线，
different locations, and different speeds.
位置不同，速度也不同。
Perhaps there's some magic
也许有某种魔力
that makes these originally different paths
这使得这些原本不同的路径
intersect here.
在此相交。
Looking back from this moment's coordinates,
从此刻的坐标回望，
let's revisit those important life milestones together.
让我们一起回顾那些重要的人生里程碑。
We might surprisingly discover their intersections.
我们可能会惊讶地发现它们的交叉点。
It's now 2014.
现在已经是2014年了。
Two young men suddenly faced life changes.
两个年轻人突然面临生活的转变。
The filter of their lives was shattered.
他们生活的过滤器被打破了。
One due to injury,
一名因受伤，
had his beloved sports career altered.
他热爱的体育事业发生了改变。
The other due to family circumstances,
另一人则因为家庭原因，
his mother took on the family's burdens.
他的母亲承担起了家庭的重担。
His mother's responsibility deeply affected him.
母亲的责任深深地影响了他。
I was the injured athlete.
我是受伤的运动员。
Because I've always been a sports student,
因为我一直是一名体育生，
and an athlete.
和一名运动员。
Once before training,
有一次训练前，
I didn't warm up properly,
我没有好好热身，
and suddenly collapsed while running.
并在奔跑时突然晕倒。
I just lay there on the track.
我只是躺在跑道上。
Then I broke down crying.
然后我就崩溃地哭了。
But I wasn't crying from pain.
但我并没有因为疼痛而哭泣。
It was because I had to rest for months.
这是因为我必须休息几个月。
I couldn't train during those months.
那几个月我无法训练。
So I thought this matter
所以我就想这件事
must be very serious.
一定很严重。
So you were a long-distance runner before?
那么您以前是一名长跑运动员吗？
Sprinting, 100-meter dash.
短跑、百米短跑。
The other one is mine
另一颗是我的
Because back in 2014
因为早在2014年
my family had some difficulties
我的家人遇到了一些困难
only my mother was there to take care of me (we relied on each other)
只有妈妈在身边照顾我（我们互相依靠）
The reason I can cook
我会做饭的原因
is because I've been cooking for myself since childhood
因为我从小就自己做饭
My ribs refuse to admit defeat
我的肋骨不肯认输
Let's leave it at that
我们就这样吧
You're no longer providing emotional support
你不再提供情感支持
I won't stir-fry later then
那我就不炒了
Yes, so during my adolescence
是的，所以在我的青春期
this experience actually influenced my whole life
这段经历实际上影响了我的一生
From that time until now
从那时到现在
no matter what difficulties I face
无论我面临什么困难
I always face them
我总是面对他们
with the same personality everyone sees in me
与每个人在我身上看到的性格相同
to deal with these matters
来处理这些事情
So I'm the kind of person who lives in the present
所以我是那种活在当下的人
No wonder
怪不得
That's good
那挺好的
Actually, I knew about Guo Xu's situation.
其实郭旭的情况我是知道的。
So when he told me about it,
所以当他告诉我这件事时
this is also why
这也是为什么
we became so close.
我们变得如此亲密。
I felt that
我觉得
he might need more attention and support.
他可能需要更多的关注和支持。
This way,
这边走，
I genuinely came to regard him as
我真的开始把他视为
a dear younger brother.
一个亲爱的弟弟。
When he mentioned this matter,
当他提到这件事的时候，
my nose immediately stung with emotion.
我的鼻子立即因激动而刺痛。
I feel that through just a few days together,
感觉在一起的短短几天，
I had completely
我已经完全
come to see Guo Xu as my
来见郭旭为我的
very dear brother.
非常亲爱的兄弟。
Yes.
是的。
Because I knew about these things,
因为我知道这些事情，
all I could do was
我所能做的就是
stand by his side and accompany him.
站在他的身边，陪伴他。
There were two girls
有两个女孩
who experienced emotional changes in 2017.
2017年经历了情绪变化。
One broke up after graduation
一个人毕业后就分手了
and resolved to start a self-media business.
并决心开创自媒体事业。
The other took a post-breakup trip
另一个则进行了分手后的旅行
and rediscovered her true self during the journey.
并在旅途中重新发现了真实的自己。
Another encountered first love,
又遇到了初恋，
but love's flavor isn't always sweet -
但爱情的味道并不总是甜蜜的
it can also be bitter.
它也可能是苦的。
I believe you've all learned
相信大家都已经学会了
to maintain independence in relationships
保持人际关系的独立性
and achieve personal growth.
并实现个人成长。
The one who broke up in 2017
2017年分手的那个
and pursued self-media was me.
而追求自媒体的就是我。
Because I used to be someone
因为我曾经是一个人
who couldn't live without being in a relationship.
没有恋爱关系就无法生活的人。
My heart felt somewhat empty,
我的心感觉有些空虚，
so I needed someone to always be with me.
所以我需要有人永远陪在我身边。
After breaking up with that boyfriend,
和那个男朋友分手后，
I realized that
我意识到
rather than exhausting myself in relationships,
而不是在人际关系中让自己疲惫不堪，
it would be better
会更好
to leave some space and time for my own growth.
给自己的成长留下一些空间和时间。
So I chose
所以我选择了
a very long period of being single.
很长一段时间都是单身。
During this single period,
在这单一时期内，
I relatively early embarked on
我比较早开始
the path of self-media.
自媒体之路。
I'm curious
我很好奇
Why did you and that boyfriend
为什么你和那个男朋友
break up back then?
当年就分手了？
Actually, we had an amicable breakup
事实上，我们友好分手了
Because this was my first time
因为这是我第一次
breaking up due to incompatible values
因价值观不兼容而分手
Because he believed
因为他相信
women should stay home to serve their husbands and raise children
妇女应该留在家里侍奉丈夫并抚养孩子
He probably had those more traditional
他可能有那些更传统的
kinds of values
价值观的种类
I felt that this way
我觉得这样
I'd have neither life nor freedom
我既没有生命，也没有自由
Freedom to me
自由给我
is extremely important
极其重要
So I couldn't accept it
所以我无法接受
After struggling with him for about
与他纠缠了大约半年后
one or two months
一两个月
we chose to separate amicably
我们选择友好分手
Then I became my own leading lady
然后我就成了自己的女主角
Yes
是的
I think she has a rich inner world
我觉得她的内心世界很丰富
She's very clear about her goals
她非常清楚自己的目标
In her choices and thoughts
在她的选择和想法中
I think she's truly remarkable
我认为她真的很了不起
Outstanding
杰出的
I was the one who took the breakup trip
我是踏上分手之旅的人
Yes, my first love lasted a year
是的，我的初恋持续了一年
Then we separated
然后我们就分开了
Weren't you saying there were no waves?
你不是说没有波浪吗？
Same one
同一个
Same one, then we parted
一样的人，然后就分手了
But before breaking up we agreed
但分手前我们都同意了
to take one last trip together
一起进行最后一次旅行
We decided to properly complete the trip
我们决定好好完成这次旅行
to give our relationship proper closure
让我们的关系得到适当的结束
before saying goodbye
在说再见之前
Then I realized this way
然后我意识到这样
we wouldn't have other
我们不会有其他的
realistic burdens or overthinking
现实的负担或过度思考
Instead, this became
相反，这变成了
the happiest time in that relationship
这段关系中最幸福的时光
I also had a long-distance relationship.
我也有过一段远距离的关系。
But after almost a year together,
但在一起快一年后，
I started noticing his attitude became strange.
我开始注意到他的态度变得奇怪。
Later I confronted him
后来我和他对峙
for an honest conversation.
进行诚实的对话。
I told him his behavior
我告诉他他的行为
was emotional neglect.
是情感上的忽视。
It really hurt me.
这真的伤害了我。
He responded by saying
他回应说
he thought our long-distance relationship wasn't realistic,
他认为我们的异地恋不现实
and we should reconsider after graduation.
毕业后我们应该重新考虑。
I was speechless.
我无语了。
Right.
正确的。
Because in relationships,
因为在人际关系中，
I give my all.
我付出我的一切。
I don't keep score.
我不记分。
I believe loving is happier than being loved.
我相信爱比被爱更幸福。
I also had a long-distance relationship.
我也有过一段远距离的关系。
It was my first romantic experience.
这是我第一次浪漫的经历。
It changed me from someone
它改变了我与某人
who was very proactive
谁非常主动
to becoming quite passive.
变得相当被动。
I was in a relationship
我正在恋爱中
that was heading toward marriage.
那是走向婚姻的。
We broke up in 2021.
我们于2021年分手。
Before that,
在此之前，
I'd never seriously dated anyone.
我从来没有认真地和任何人约会过。
This relationship impacted me deeply.
这段感情对我影响很深。
Profoundly.
深刻。
It taught me how to love someone
它教会了我如何去爱一个人
and what love truly means.
以及爱的真正含义。
I came to Beijing
我来了北京
and began a new campus life
并开始了新的校园生活
You know, being away from home
你知道，远离家乡
emotionally
情感上地
I needed something to hold onto
我需要一些东西来抓住
So very quickly
所以很快
within the first month of school
开学第一个月内
I found myself in a campus romance
我发现自己陷入了校园恋情
I think that for me
我认为对我来说
it was a very important part of life
这是生活中非常重要的一部分
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
Did you find that feeling here
你在这里找到那种感觉了吗
that you had back in school days?
你上学时有过吗？
Yes, with you guys it's very...
是的，和你们在一起真的很...
Playing basketball together
一起打篮球
one-on-one games
一对一的游戏
Right
正确的
Okay, let me help you again
好的，我再帮你一下
No
不
This kind of communal living
这种集体生活
is something you only experience in student days
是只有在学生时代才能经历的事情
This lifestyle
这种生活方式
The bonds here are the most genuine and pure
这里的羁绊是最真挚、最纯粹的
Thank you to the production team
感谢制作团队
Truly
确实
And walking on the beach at night
还有晚上在沙滩上散步
feels just like walking on the school playground
感觉就像走在学校操场上一样
It's the same
是一样的
Exactly the same
完全一样
Yes.
是的。
When I saw everyone's faces,
当我看到大家的表情时
those pure smiles and joy,
那些纯净的笑容和快乐，
I truly couldn't imagine
我实在无法想象
us not having this living environment.
我们没有这样的生活环境。
When we return to our respective posts to work,
当我们回到各自的岗位工作时，
what kind of emotions we'd feel then.
那时我们会感受到什么样的情感。
I'd feel a kind of fear toward those emotions.
我会对这些情绪感到一种恐惧。
I think having such companions,
我想，有这样的同伴，
spending so many days together,
一起度过了这么多天，
was truly wonderful.
真的很棒。
Truly.
确实。
In 2022, someone made their screen debut,
2022年，有人首次登上银幕，
regretting not showing their best self.
后悔没有展现最好的自己。
I actually think that version of me
我实际上认为那个版本的我
was somewhat arrogant.
就有些嚣张了。
So I deeply regret it to this day.
所以我至今都深感后悔。
But ever since then,
但从那时起，
I've taken everything very seriously.
我非常认真地对待一切。
Once I set a goal, I must achieve it.
一旦我设定了目标，我就必须实现它。
Someone faced a loved one's passing,
有人面对亲人的去世，
regretting not spending more time with their grandfather.
后悔没有花更多时间陪伴祖父。
Learning to say goodbye is also an important life lesson.
学会说再见也是重要的人生课程。
My grandfather's passing was
我祖父的去世是
Then
然后
When I was just born
我刚出生的时候
my grandfather held me in his arms
我的祖父把我抱在怀里
and proudly showed me to everyone
并自豪地向大家展示我
He was so, so proud.
他是那么的骄傲。
During the time he was ill
在他生病期间
I was studying abroad in Canada
我在加拿大留学
because my mother didn’t want me
因为我妈妈不想要我
to worry too much
担心太多
She just told me that grandfather
她刚刚告诉我祖父
wasn’t feeling very well
感觉不太舒服
and was a little sick.
并且有点不舒服。
Then, after about a week
然后，大约一周后
my mother told me he had passed away.
我母亲告诉我他去世了。
At that time, I couldn’t do anything
那时我什么也做不了
because I was in Canada.
因为我在加拿大。
Sorry
对不起
But I believe that one day
但我相信有一天
I will meet him again
我会再次遇见他
He just went to heaven
他刚刚去了天堂
Preparing our home for us
为我们准备我们的家
Packing things
包装东西
It's alright, don't feel sorry.
没关系，不用感到遗憾。
On Tianping Island,
在天平岛上，
most people
大多数人
are new friends meeting for the first time.
是第一次见面的新朋友。
But some share a special connection.
但有些人有着特殊的联系。
Hello, old friend.
你好，老朋友。
Is this about me and Hu Wei?
这是我和胡伟的事吗？
Yes.
是的。
Hu Wei and I are actually friends in private.
我和胡伟私下里其实是朋友。
And I genuinely didn’t know she’d participate.
我真的不知道她会参加。
I can vouch—I didn’t know either.
我可以保证——我也不知道。
So on the first day,
于是第一天，
seeing her so poised,
看到她如此泰然自若的样子
I really wasn’t used to it.
我实在不习惯。
You know,
你知道，
Hello everyone, I’m Xiao Enya.
大家好，我是肖恩雅。
Or just Yaya.
或者只是亚亚。
You can't just film this randomly
你不能随意拍摄这个
It's quite awkward
实在是太尴尬了
But actually we've never had
但其实我们从来没有过
For example, shared experiences
例如，分享经验
Like going on trips together
喜欢一起去旅行
Right
正确的
But this particular trip
但这次特别的旅行
Made me realize
让我意识到
That we're actually very similar people
我们实际上是非常相似的人
Extremely similar
极其相似
In some ways
在某些方面
Yes
是的
Our personalities are somewhat alike too
我们的性格也有些相似
About our personalities, I should clarify
关于我们的性格，我应该澄清一下
I don't have her...
我没有她...
I'm a bit more lively
我比较活泼一点
But not to that extreme
但没到那么极端
Through this experience
通过这次经历
I've come to realize
我已经意识到
Xiao Enya is a very charming girl
肖恩雅是一个很有魅力的女孩
I wasn't asking you
我不是在问你
Wasn't asking you, okay?
不是问你好吗？
Xiao Enya has her sensitive
小恩雅有她的敏感
And delicate side
还有精致的一面
And also her contrasting charm
还有她的反差魅力
You too
你也是
Mutual flattery
互相阿谀奉承
Can't keep up with this banter
跟不上这个玩笑
Then elaborate more
然后再详细说明一下
I and Chen Guanyu
我和陈冠宇
met around fourth or fifth grade in elementary school
小学四年级或五年级左右认识
Actually before the show
其实在演出之前
I knew he would be coming
我知道他会来
Because we knew the same clothing supplier
因为我们认识同一家服装供应商
We both asked if there were clothes we could borrow
我们都问有没有衣服可以借
Then the supplier said
然后供应商说
"What's going on with you and Chen Guanyu?"
“你和陈冠宇到底是怎么回事？”
"Why are you both asking me this at the same time?"
“你们为什么同时问我这个？”
That's how we recognized each other
就这样我们认出了彼此
Right
正确的
I actually met Gu Zhenxiang two years ago too
其实我两年前也认识过顾振翔
We worked together
我们一起工作
on shooting a commercial
在拍摄广告时
But when I knew you were coming
但当我知道你要来的时候
I felt very at ease
我感到很安心
You gave me a sense of security, you know?
你给了我安全感，你知道吗？
There's something about it
有一些关于它的事情
But not just because I was here
但不仅仅是因为我在这里
I also gave you a lot of security
我也给了你很多安全感
You could say that if you want
你可以说如果你愿意的话
Putting on airs
摆架子
Now we're putting on airs
现在我们摆架子
Yeah
是的
I need some security in my comfort zone first
我首先需要在自己的舒适区获得一些安全感
before showing my true personality
在展现我的真实个性之前
Now it's being a bit too freely shown
现在它的表现有点过于自由了
Same
相同的
Same here
同样在这里
Okay, you hurt me
好吧，你伤害了我
Good, that's interesting
不错，很有趣
I heard Chen Menger and Gu Zhenxiang
我听到陈梦儿和顾振翔
met before too, right?
以前也见过吧？
Yes
是的
Gu Zhenxiang and I just met briefly
我和顾振祥只是短暂认识
Just once
就一次
The night before we came to Sanya
来三亚的前一天晚上
we went to see a show together
我们一起去看演出
I almost had that with her too
我也差点和她发生过这样的事
I almost went too
我也差点去了
But we really don't remember
但我们真的不记得了
Too many people
人太多了
Only after arriving here did we realize
到了这里才发现
we had taken photos together
我们一起拍过照片
It's really quite fateful
实在是太有缘分了
Yes
是的
Lu Wanfei and I have met before too.
我和陆婉菲也见过面。
Just once in passing.
只是路过一次。
You've met Lu Wanfei too?
You've met Lu Wanfei too?
Yes, I've met Guo Xu.
是的，我见过郭旭。
You guys are ridiculous.
你们真是可笑。
This is really unbelievable.
这真是令人难以置信。
Honestly, this is so absurd, everyone.
老实说，大家这太荒谬了。
When I first saw her on this show,
当我第一次在这个节目中看到她的时候
I felt like I'd seen her somewhere before.
我感觉我以前在哪里见过她。
I asked where she usually lives.
我问她平时住在哪里。
She said Beijing.
她说北京。
I mentioned I went to Beijing on business in January.
我提到我一月份去北京出差。
Worked out at China World Trade Center.
在中国国际贸易中心锻炼。
Then we realized at that gym,
然后我们在那个健身房意识到，
our stories matched up.
我们的故事很吻合。
We'd actually crossed paths there.
我们实际上在那里有过交集。
Because her face really left an impression on me.
因为她的脸确实给我留下了深刻的印象。
May I ask why you remembered her?
请问你为什么记得她？
Because she's so tall. I'm too tall.
因为她太高了。我太高了。
Right, because that gym...
是的，因为那个健身房...
What about the gym?
健身房呢？
What is it, may I ask?
请问是什么？
That's Beijing's most famous
这是北京最出名的
trendy influencer gym.
时尚有影响力的健身房。
Yes, full of beautiful women.
是的，到处都是美女。
But there are quite a few handsome guys too
但也有不少帅哥
Xiao Enya, how come you...
小恩雅，你怎么……
...didn't show even a hint of "killing intent"?
……连一丝“杀意”都没有表现出来吗？
What killing intent?
什么杀意？
What kind of people are we anyway?
我们到底是什么样的人？
Aries - we're both fine.
白羊座——我们都很好。
Whatever, as long as we're happy.
不管怎样，只要我们幸福就好。
Whatever.
任何。
What a coincidence, really quite a coincidence.
真是太巧了，真是太巧了。
How could you remember for so long?
你怎么能记得这么久？
That's quite impressive.
这真是令人印象深刻。
Right.
正确的。
This January I went on a business trip.
今年一月我出差了。
Actually not far.
其实不远。
Xiao Enya.
Xiao Enya.
Come...
来...
...back to reality.
...回到现实。
Come back.
回来。
It's good.
很好。
Really.
真的。
After this, let's meet up more often.
以后我们就多见面吧。
Yes.
是的。
You know, before I...
你知道，在我...
...had never experienced this kind of group life.
……从来没有经历过这样的集体生活。
That's right.
这是正确的。
I never went to summer camps as a kid.
我小时候从未参加过夏令营。
Or anything like that.
或者类似的东西。
So I feel that after growing up...
所以我觉得长大后...
...especially after fighting alone...
……尤其是在独自战斗之后……
You lose the ability to...
你失去了...的能力
...get along with groups of people.
……与一群人相处。
Right.
正确的。
So now I'm...
所以现在我...
...replenishing my emotional value.
...补充我的情感价值。
Giving everyone more energy.
给大家更多的能量。
Isn't this working?
这不行吗？
Two emotional values.
两种情感价值。
Emotion Brother One, Emotion Brother Two.
情感一哥，情感二哥。
Both fully charged.
两者都充满电。
I'm not just talking about Jiang Shangru
我说的不只是姜尚儒
It's that I feel within this group
这就是我在这个群体中的感觉
I can truly feel everyone's enthusiasm
我能真切地感受到大家的热情
So you've all given me tremendous energy
所以你们都给了我巨大的能量
That's right
这是正确的
Thank you
谢谢
Getting deep there, sis
深入那里，姐姐
Getting profound
变得深刻
Let's keep it casual
让我们保持随意
Elevated
高架
On the first day there was this
第一天有这个
awkwardness between strangers
陌生人之间的尴尬
By the last day there was this
到了最后一天，出现了这样的情况
awkwardness from being too familiar
因过于熟悉而感到尴尬
Everyone's just so interesting
每个人都那么有趣
There's this feeling of
有这样的感觉
old classmates reuniting after many years
老同学多年后重逢
coming together to film something
聚在一起拍摄某事
The time now comes to
现在到了
March 29, 2024
2024 年 3 月 29 日
Starting from this gesture of love
从这一份爱的举动开始
You officially begin
你正式开始
your life on Balance Island
您在平衡岛上的生活
Let's raise our glasses together
让我们一起举起酒杯
Cheers
干杯
These twelve days
这十二天
may not seem long
可能看起来不长
but they've left deep imprints in our hearts
但他们却在我们心中留下了深深的印记
Rock, paper, scissors
石头、剪刀、布
Though brief, these twelve days together
虽然短暂，但这十二天的相处
were enough for us to bond and understand each other deeply
足以让我们加深彼此的联系和了解
The honor is mine
荣誉是我的
This is today's groom
这是今天的新郎
Yes, the groom
是的，新郎
During these twelve days
这十二天里
what stories have we experienced
我们经历了哪些故事
what moving moments have we cherished
我们珍惜哪些感人的时刻
Now, time stands still
现在，时间静止了
Please come forward one by one, islanders
请岛民们一一站出来
to receive your personal Balance Island Love Report
接收您的个人平衡岛爱情报告
Alright, I'm going.
好吧，我这就去。
Daniel's Tianping Island Love Report
丹尼尔的天平岛爱情报告
Hello, Daniel
你好，丹尼尔
March 29, 2024
2024 年 3 月 29 日
was your first day on Tianping Island
是你在天平岛的第一天
My name is Dandan
我叫丹丹
That day
当天
you broke down from struggling to adapt
你因努力适应而崩溃
Someone extended kindness to you
有人向你表达善意
What's wrong?
怎么了？
From then on
从此
every day you spent on Tianping Island
你在天平岛度过的每一天
you were inseparable from her
你和她形影不离
On your fifth day on Tianping Island
来到天平岛的第五天
you had a special off-island date
你有一个特别的离岛约会
and met a new girl, Chen Menger
并认识了一个新女孩，陈梦儿
But after the whole date
但整个约会结束后
you seemed only concerned about
你似乎只关心
whether your swimming form was correct
你的游泳姿势是否正确
Do you remember that seaside talk?
你还记得那次海边谈话吗？
I believe you've also been searching for answers within your heart
相信你内心也一直在寻找答案
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Exclusive favor
独家优惠
Please check your Tianping Island keywords
请检查您的天平岛关键字
Off-track
偏离轨道
I feel
我感觉
the description perfectly captures how I've been these past few days
这个描述完美地描述了我过去几天的情况
After arriving on this island
到达这个岛后
I've constantly felt somewhat lost
我时常感到有些失落
I've never experienced this kind of life before
我以前从未经历过这样的生活
Even now
即使现在
I still get quite nervous
我还是很紧张
During these twelve days
这十二天里
I've gone through many emotional ups and downs
我经历过很多情感的起伏
and frequently felt insecure
并经常感到不安全
My heart has been in a very complicated state
我的心一直处于一种很复杂的状态
I want to thank He Jinyi
我要感谢何锦仪
because she created for me here
因为她在这里为我创造了
a safe space that belongs to me
属于我的安全空间
And secondly, thank you Fu Jie
其次谢谢付洁
and Tao Zhi
and Tao Zhi
And these other brothers
还有其他这些兄弟
Help me gradually
逐渐帮助我
integrate better with everyone
与大家更好地融合
He Jinyi's Love Report from Tianping Island
何锦仪天平岛爱情报告
Hello, He Jinyi
何锦仪你好
You are Tianping Island's
你是天平岛的
first to extend a helping hand to others
首先向别人伸出援助之手
Your kindness
你的善意
not only comforted them but was also reciprocated
不仅安慰了他们，还得到了回报
On the second day at Tianping Island
天平岛第二天
With your remarkable memory
凭借你非凡的记忆力
despite your team's disadvantage
尽管你的球队处于劣势
you secured a comeback victory
你取得了翻盘的胜利
and earned the right to make your own choices
并赢得了做出自己选择的权利
This was undoubtedly your
这无疑是你的
brightest moment on Tianping Island
天平岛上最闪亮的时刻
You were distracted all day because of someone
你一整天都因为某人而心烦意乱
but also smiled because of them
也因为他们而微笑
I miss you
我想你
Me too
我也是
You struggled with the relationship
你在这段关系中挣扎
Honest expression means everything to you
诚实的表达对你来说意味着一切
I'm strong-willed inside
我内心意志坚强
I can't tolerate any flaws
我无法容忍任何瑕疵
Love is truly a bit like a tornado
爱情确实有点像龙卷风
It comes swiftly
它来得很快
Whether you can hold onto it depends on yourself
能不能坚持就看你自己了
To enjoy the moment or pursue eternity
享受当下还是追求永恒
What would your answer be?
你的答案是什么？
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Daring to love and hate
敢爱敢恨
Your Tianping Island keywords
您的天平岛关键词
Favoritism
偏爱
That gave me goosebumps all over
这让我全身起鸡皮疙瘩
Who wrote this?
这是谁写的？
So skillful, I want one too
太有才了，我也想要一个
Truly well-written
确实写得很好
Impressive
感人的
I want one too, I'm serious
我也想要一个，我是认真的
I got goosebumps
我起鸡皮疙瘩
A love letter
一封情书
Touching
接触
Yes
是的
Hello, Xiao Enya
你好，小恩雅
During the twelve days spent on Tianping Island
在天平岛度过的十二天
You achieved a victory in a partner mission
您在合作伙伴任务中取得了胜利
Thus earning you an off-island date
从而为您赢得一次离岛约会机会
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Were you happy that day?
那天你开心吗？
I want some too
我也想要一些
Two straws
两根吸管
You drink first
你先喝
Tianping Islanders care deeply about their appearance
天平岛人非常注重自己的外表
Yet you stood out by not washing your hair for four days
然而你却因四天不洗头而脱颖而出
Why must you bring this up?
为什么一定要提这个？
But fortunately
但幸运的是
Someone who can’t stand others skipping hair washes for three days
无法忍受别人三天不洗头的人
Never judged you for it
从未因此评判过你
Instead, you often rolled your eyes at them
相反，你经常对他们翻白眼
Far too often
太频繁了
The fourth day on Tianping Island
天平岛第四天
You and him took eight minutes
你和他花了八分钟
to complete the默契考验默契 test
to complete the默契考验默契 test
making it the longest time among all partners
是所有合作伙伴中时间最长的
In other words, your默契度默契 is zero
In other words, your默契度默契 is zero
You're not someone who comforts others
你不是一个会安慰别人的人
yet you happened to partner with a crybaby
但你却碰巧和一个爱哭鬼搭档
Alright
好吧
Don't cry, okay?
别哭，好吗？
The ninth day on Tianping Island
天平岛第九天
You said the most comforting words
你说了最安慰的话
within your capability
在你的能力范围内
Wipe your tears
擦干你的眼泪
Really, I'm not good with words
真的，我不善言辞
The journey on Tianping Island is ending
天平岛之旅即将结束
What you left here most was laughter
你在这里留下最多的是笑声
Your laughter echoed through the skies
你的笑声响彻天空
Tianping Island thanks you for coming
天平岛感谢您的光临
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
is being yourself
就是做你自己
Right
正确的
Here are your Tianping Island keywords
这是您的天平岛关键词
Never pretentious
从不做作
Cool
凉爽的
I feel like no one has ever understood me like this
我感觉从来没有人这样理解过我
I think there's a great line following it
我认为它后面有一条很棒的线
which is "be yourself"
这就是“做你自己”
Including the keyword "never pretentious"
包括“从不做作”这个关键词
It actually resembles me
它实际上很像我
Yes
是的
But many might say about this aspect
但很多人可能会说这方面
No one at work can understand
工作中没人能理解
Great
伟大的
I really like it
我真的很喜欢它
Guo Xu's Tianping Island Love Report
Guo Xu's Tianping Island Love Report
Hello, Guo Xu
Hello, Guo Xu
You might not remember
你可能不记得了
the first person you met on the island
你在岛上遇到的第一个人
was Xiao Enya
是肖恩雅
Hello
你好
Slow down, be careful
慢点，小心
You gallantly offered her your arm
你勇敢地向她伸出手臂
And walked your first beach path together
一起走过你们的第一条海滩小路
During your later trip to Tianping Island
稍后前往天平岛时
Did you walk that path again?
你又走那条路了吗？
You walked it every night
你每晚都走过
The fourth day on the island
上岛第四天
You've already identified the girl who makes your heart flutter
你已经找到了让你心动的女孩
I'm begging you, I'm not that delicate
我求求你了，我没那么脆弱
I'm begging you
我求你了
That night at 11:30 PM
当晚 11:30 PM
You were on Tianping Island
你在天平岛
Frantically calling and searching for someone's name
疯狂地打电话并搜索某人的名字
From then on, your scales tipped only for her
从此你的天平只为她倾斜
Where are you sitting? I'll sit beside you
你坐在哪里？我会坐在你旁边
Just like that
就这样
No
不
Hurry
匆忙
I'll do nineteen, you just do one
我做十九个，你只做一个
In the world of love
在爱情的世界里
You should be the one closest to authenticity
你应该是最接近真实的人
Your honesty lets you talk about exes without hesitation
你的诚实让你可以毫不犹豫地谈论前任
While sweating bullets for you
为你流汗的同时
I'm also glad you've made it this far
我也很高兴你已经做到了这一步
without being eliminated from the island
不被岛上淘汰
You said
你说
You're the best at taking photos of girls
你最擅长给女孩拍照了
Your photography skills surpass
你的摄影技术超越
99% of boyfriends nationwide
全国99%的男朋友
But in practice
但在实践中
You've repeatedly made your crush
你已经多次让你暗恋的人
angry and dissatisfied
愤怒和不满
Now raise your hand
现在举起你的手
Touch your ridiculously handsome left cheek
摸摸你英俊得可笑的左脸颊
Does it sting a little?
有一点刺痛吗？
Maybe getting humbled is a required lesson on Tianping Island
也许谦卑是天平岛的必修课
Even though you said
尽管你说
You can't stand girls who don't wash their hair for three days
你受不了三天不洗头的女孩
But your standards
但你的标准
stretched from three to four days
从三天延长到四天
then to five
然后到五
Raise your hand and touch your right cheek
举起手，摸摸右脸颊
Is it as swollen as the left one?
和左边一样肿吗？
Of course, love has no rules
当然，爱情是没有规则的
You're Tianping Island's
你是天平岛的
most genuine and pure "happy puppy"
最真实最纯粹的“快乐小狗”
Even after leaving the island
即使离开了小岛
I hope you and your crush
我希望你和你的暗恋对象
find happiness together
一起寻找幸福
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Joy above all
欢乐高于一切
Here’s your Tianping Island keyword
这是您的天平岛关键字
Enya
恩雅
Receive your Tianping Island keyword
接收您的天平岛关键词
"The old father" expressed complete satisfaction
“老父亲”表示完全满意
This is written so brilliantly
这篇写得太精彩了
Openly declaring satisfaction
公开表示满意
"The old father" openly expressed satisfaction
“老父亲”公开表示满意
Extremely satisfied
非常满意
I think this final "Enya"
我认为最后的“Enya”
Elevated it to another level
将其提升到了另一个层次
Maxed out, truly maxed out
极限了，真的极限了
Keywords fully maximized
关键词完全最大化
Way too maxed out
太极限了
Absolutely amazing
绝对惊人
Here we go
开始了
Hu Wei's Tianping Island Love Report
胡伟的天平岛爱情报告
Hello, Hu Wei (Nannan)
Hello, Hu Wei (Nannan)
You were the first resident to land on Tianping Island
你是第一个登陆天平岛的居民
As the undisputed queen of sweet-and-spicy introductions
作为无可争议的甜辣入门女王
Has your gaze
有你的目光
lingered on the two men who followed?
还在追随的两个男人身上徘徊？
Perhaps the scale's sway was predestined
或许天平的摇摆早已注定
In the scales of preference
在偏好范围内
you once consistently placed weights for one person
你曾经一直为一个人举重
Have you now made him understand
你现在让他明白了吗
that love is preference, honesty, and above all, courage
爱是偏好、诚实，最重要的是勇气
If beauty were a person's adjective
如果美丽是一个人的形容词
But beauty is your least remarkable trait
但美丽是你最不显着的特质
You are truly the undisputed makeup king of Balance Island
你真是平衡岛无可争议的彩妆王
You're also the best listener for others' emotions
你也是别人情绪最好的倾听者
Sincere and brave Nannan
真诚勇敢的楠楠
Clear-minded and independent Nannan
思路清晰、独立的楠楠
Capable-of-anything Nannan
无所不能的楠楠
Which window of yours was truly closed?
你的哪扇窗户是真正关着的？
The adventure on Balance Island is nearing its end
平衡岛的冒险已接近尾声
Beyond Balance Island
超越平衡岛
How will you continue your journey of love?
你将如何继续你的爱情之旅？
Please remember to send
请记得发送
continuous updates of your love to Balance Island
持续更新你对平衡岛的喜爱
May you find the best version of yourself on life's journey
愿你在人生的旅途中找到最好的自己
Your Balance Island spirit
您的平衡岛精神
Rising to meet "Nan" (challenges)
奋起迎接“南”（挑战）
Please check your Balance Island keywords
请检查您的平衡岛关键字
Caught between "Nan" (difficult choices)
夹在“难”之间（艰难的选择）
So skilled
太熟练了
Incredibly talented
才华横溢
Super representative
超级代表
This is truly super representative
这真的超级有代表性
Really knows how to write
真的很会写
Indeed when I first arrived
确实我刚来的时候
Because I was
因为我当时
more familiar with the two boys sitting beside me
更熟悉坐在我旁边的两个男孩
So I was balancing my scales
所以我正在平衡我的天平
But now I've made him understand
但现在我已经让他明白了
Love is preference, honesty, and courage
爱是偏爱、诚实和勇气
So nervous
好紧张
Jiang Shangru's Love Report on Tianping Island
姜尚如天平岛爱情报告
Hello, Jiang Shangru
蒋尚儒你好
Do you remember how you looked when you first arrived on the island?
你还记得你第一次来到岛上时的样子吗？
Unconsciously
不知不觉
You've already lived on Tianping Island for twelve days
你已经在天平岛生活了十二天
Daylight doesn't understand the darkness of night
白天无法理解夜晚的黑暗
A kaleidoscopic darkness
万花筒般的黑暗
Your skin is getting darker
你的皮肤越来越黑
It's proof of your life
这是你一生的证明
on this island
在这个岛上
At first
起初
you said you were here to win
你说你来这里是为了胜利
and would definitely take first place
并且肯定会获得第一名
But on the second day here
但来到这里的第二天
you already failed to get first place
你已经没能获得第一名了
Had a
有一个
restless, sleepless terrible night
不安、失眠的可怕夜晚
Upon learning Hu Wei went off-island for a date
得知胡伟出岛约会
Your expression seemed incredulous
你的表情似乎难以置信
Plus the double blow of being "stabbed in the back"
加上“背后捅刀子”的双重打击
Love is a hand that reaches out but then withdraws
爱是一只伸出去又缩回的手
But fortunately you remained steadfast
但庆幸的是你依然坚定
You're truly great, you're always so early
你真是太棒了，总是这么早
This might be my only move left
这可能是我剩下的唯一举动
Only my shamelessness and courage remain
只剩下我的无耻和勇敢
Suddenly receiving heart-shaped chocolates
突然收到心形巧克力
So delicious
真好吃
Your personal makeup touch-up artist during game breaks
比赛休息期间您的私人化妆师
Through these actions
通过这些行动
You search for signs of their affection toward you
你寻找他们对你的感情的迹象
On the seventh day
第七天
You've finally won the competition
你终于赢得了比赛
And earned yourself
并为自己赢得了
A romantic and joyful off-island dating trip
一次浪漫欢乐的离岛约会之旅
Brother
兄弟
Mom, I'm going on a date
妈妈，我要去约会
That day, you said "you're beautiful" three times
那天你说了三遍“你很漂亮”
Four times "you're wonderful"
四次“你真棒”
Five times "you're truly charming"
五次“你真的很有魅力”
Every smile from them
他们的每一个微笑
Could capture your complete infatuation
能俘获你彻底的痴情
Every time the scales of preference tilted
每当偏好的天平倾斜时
You would without hesitation
你会毫不犹豫
Wholeheartedly choose the same name
一心选择同名
Hu Wei
Hu Wei
Is Hu Wei here?
胡伟在吗？
You defeated
你打败了
99.99% of the islanders
99.99%的岛民
Becoming the only one on the island
成为岛上唯一的人
Who from beginning to end
从头到尾是谁
Remained devoted to just one person
只为一个人专一
Love is eternal while it lasts
爱若持续，便是永恒
I believe you've found the answer you sought
我相信您已经找到了您想要的答案
Jiang Shangru, born for love
江尚儒，为爱而生
You can also be the embodiment of love
你也可以是爱的化身
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Courage
勇气
Please receive your Tianping Island keyword
请收到您的天平岛关键词
Nan Nan
在 在 在
Your Tianping Island keyword
您的天平岛关键字
Vote for me
投票给我
You want me to vote for you
你想让我投票给你
You'll definitely vote for me
你一定会投票给我
So how many votes do you think I'll give you?
那么你认为我会给你多少票？
If you don't give me four votes
如果你不给我四票
you're "dead"
你“死了”
This one is a bit too white
这个有点太白了
This is for a date
这是为了约会
I want to stand out
我想脱颖而出
I think you're shining right now
我觉得你现在很闪耀
I deserve this
这是我应得的
This is what we made for each other
这是我们为彼此所做的
A very obvious heart
非常明显的心
Why do I feel like what I wrote
为什么我感觉像我写的
makes me seem like a total "love-struck fool"
让我看起来像个彻头彻尾的“痴情傻瓜”
plus someone with really dark skin
再加上皮肤很黑的人
That's exactly it
就是这样
Not sure about "love-struck fool" but the dark skin
不知道是不是“痴情傻瓜”，但皮肤黝黑
is definitely pretty dark
绝对是很暗
Actually, I really don't want today to end
其实我真的不想今天结束
It's not sadness, just reluctance to let go
不是悲伤，只是不愿放手
Because
因为
I genuinely love from the bottom of my heart
我是从心底里真心地爱着
the feeling of everyone being together
大家在一起的感觉
Whether eating, playing games
无论是吃饭、玩游戏
or even going on dates
甚至去约会
I just really love
我真的很爱
the energy when everyone gathers together
大家聚集在一起时的能量
I think the last day is actually quite...
我觉得最后一天真的很...
quite something
相当的东西
Yeah
是的
Thank you, we really like you too
谢谢你，我们也很喜欢你
I like it too
我也喜欢
Careful
小心
She fits in so well here.
她很适合这里。
Truly, a flower fairy.
果然是花仙子。
Perfect match.
完美搭配。
Weng Fanxi's Love Report from Tianping Island
翁凡西天平岛爱情报告
Hello, Weng Fanxi
Hello, Weng Fanxi
On your first day at Tianping Island
来到天平岛的第一天
Dressed in an elegant qipao
身着优雅旗袍
you won the favor of four men
你赢得了四个男人的青睐
We wonder if you were thinking
我们想知道您是否在想
"My charm is truly unmatched"
“我的魅力真是无与伦比”
or just wanting to escape this deserted island
或者只是想逃离这个荒岛
You never missed your daily nap
你从来没有错过每天的小睡
From you, we learned
从你身上，我们学到了
that true beauty requires good sleep
真正的美丽需要良好的睡眠
You're always
你总是
on the front lines observing others' romances
在前线观察别人的恋情
Wherever there's gossip
凡是有闲言碎语的地方
there you are with sharp questions
你有尖锐的问题
You're undoubtedly the gossip queen of Tianping Island
你无疑是天平岛的绯闻女王
During your time on Tianping Island
在天平岛期间
you experienced three island dates in total
你一共经历了三次海岛约会
From the first dramatic "three-person scene"
从第一个戏剧性的“三人场景”开始
to the second peaceful time for two
到了两人的第二个平静时光
I toss my hair, free from romantic troubles
我甩甩头发，摆脱浪漫的烦恼
And the final island date
以及最终的岛屿日期
did it leave you with unique memories?
有没有给你留下独特的回忆呢？
During off-island missions
执行离岛任务时
with zero success rate you became
你的成功率为零
one of only two girls without off-island dates
仅有的两个没有出岛约会的女孩之一
Each time the off-island list was announced
每次公布离岛名单
it wasn't a romantic fanfare that sounded
听起来并不是浪漫的号角
but the sound of your broken spirit
但你破碎的精神的声音
My Tianping Island spirit
我的天平岛精神
Lying flat
平躺
Please check my Tianping Island keywords
请查看我的天平岛关键词
Want to leave the island
想要离开这个岛
Actually
实际上
It aligns well with my personal mindset
很符合我个人的心态
But right now, I don’t really want to leave the island
但现在我真的不想离开这个岛
Instead, I want to say
相反，我想说
If we could have a few more days
如果我们能再多几天时间
Stay here a little longer
在这里多呆一会儿
It would be great to spend more time with everyone
如果能花更多的时间和大家在一起就好了
Let's go
我们走吧
Move out
搬出
Depart
出发
Zheng Dedong is so cool
Zheng Dedong is so cool
Zheng Dedong's Love Report from Tianping Island
郑德东天平岛爱情报道
Hello Zheng Dedong (Duoduo)
Hello Zheng Dedong (Duoduo)
When we first met
当我们第一次见面时
The person sitting and chatting with you was
坐着和你聊天的人是
Weng Fanxi (Banban)
Weng Fanxi (Banban)
Do you still often sit together and chat?
你们还经常坐在一起聊天吗？
First time seeing so many
第一次见这么多
Handsome and beautiful humans
又帅又美丽的人类
Humans
人类
On your third day on the island
在岛上的第三天
You had your first island date
你第一次岛上约会
Remember the magic trick she performed for you?
还记得她为你表演的魔术吗？
Let me do another magic trick for you
让我再给你表演一个魔术
More magic tricks
更多魔术
In the scales of preference
在偏好范围内
You always voted for the same person
你总是投票给同一个人
We won't say who she is
我们不会说她是谁
During your time on Tianping Island
在天平岛期间
You never left the island
你从未离开过这座岛
You were a dedicated island keeper
你是一位尽职尽责的岛屿守护者
Island Master
岛主
As the only local guy on the island
作为岛上唯一的当地人
You often mentioned the joy of "watching drama"
您经常提到“看剧”的乐趣
It's raining
下雨了
Date's canceled
日期已取消
Hope everyone can have fun
希望大家都能玩得开心
But I'm feeling terrible
但我感觉很糟糕
Let me pour some for He Jinyi
我给何锦衣倒点
She's been wanting coconut juice
她一直想要椰子汁
Everything's about He Jinyi
一切都是关于何瑾怡的
I do all the work here
我在这里做所有的工作
And still get emotionally attacked
仍然受到情感攻击
And you've repeatedly given
而你也曾多次给予
dating advice to your bros
给你兄弟的约会建议
You're truly the love strategist
你真是爱情策略师
Chasing girls is exhausting
追女生好累
Just like exercising
就像锻炼身体一样
If you do it too fast, you'll get tired
如果你做得太快，你会很累
Have a proper face-to-face talk
进行适当的面对面交谈
Every journey has its regrets, okay?
每一段旅程都有遗憾，好吗？
Don't call me strategist
别叫我战略家
Just call me matchmaker
就叫我红娘吧
But you probably never imagined
但你可能万万没想到
You'd become gossip material for others
你会成为别人的八卦材料
Though you never left the island
虽然你从未离开过这座岛
You still managed to have
你仍然设法拥有
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
I hope you can always maintain the "spectator" mentality
希望大家始终保持“旁观者”心态
when facing this world
当面对这个世界时
Move forward without looking back
不回头地向前走
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
"Being a spectator"
“作为一个旁观者”
Your Tianping Island keyword
您的天平岛关键字
Love strategist
爱情策略师
One who wants to leave the island
一个想要离开这个岛的人
I think "gossiping" really suits him
我觉得“八卦”很适合他
"Gossiping"
“八卦”
Indeed
的确
When I got this love report
当我收到这份爱情报告时
I felt that
我觉得
Actually, "gossiping" is truly my
其实“八卦”确实是我的
Tianping Island's spirit
天平岛的精神
But I think
但我认为
My Tianping Island keyword
我的天平岛 关键词
Can also be described as "gossiping"
也可以用“八卦”来形容
During our night chats with everyone
晚上和大家聊天的时候
I collect these "gossip sources"
我收集这些“八卦消息来源”
Right
正确的
These twelve days have been magical
这十二天很神奇
The greatest gain has been
最大的收获就是
You good brothers
你们好兄弟
Wow
哇
Lu Wanfei's Love Report from Tianping Island
陆婉菲天平岛爱情报告
The first island survival battle after arriving
抵达后的第一场海岛生存战
You and your gaming partner Zhang Xin lost the game
你和你的游戏搭档张欣输掉了比赛
But won hotpot
但赢了火锅
If you get the chance to visit Chongqing
如果你有机会来重庆
Would you embark on this spicy journey?
你愿意踏上这段辛辣的旅程吗？
People gradually left
人们渐渐离开
It seems to have become
似乎已经成为了
A burden you dare not speak of to others
不敢对别人说起的负担
It also let us see the little girl inside you
也让我们看到了你内心的小女孩
Perhaps it was these pressures
也许正是这些压力
That made your life on the island
这成就了你在岛上的生活
Constantly about survival
始终关注生存
To others it looked like romance
对其他人来说这看起来像是浪漫
But for you
但对于你来说
It was an adventure where no one should be absent
这是一场谁都不应缺席的冒险
Thank you for that orange sunset on the bench
谢谢你在长凳上看到橙色的夕阳
Need me to pull you up?
需要我拉你起来吗？
First time I've felt this place was so beautiful
第一次觉得这个地方这么美
Yes
是的
He made you remove your heart's armor
他让你卸下心上的铠甲
Made pink bubbles appear around you
让你的周围出现粉红色的泡泡
Out of three partner missions
三项合作伙伴任务中
You teamed up with him twice
你和他联手两次
As the best partners
作为最好的合作伙伴
Keep it up
继续努力吧
Your chemistry reached 100%
你们的化学反应达到100%
Combat ability surpassed
战斗力超越
40% of the island's residents
岛上40%的居民
You went on three dates total
你总共约会了三次
A swaying scale always demands a choice between two sides
摇摆的天平总是需要在两侧之间做出选择
You are summer
你是夏天
Forever vibrant
永远充满活力
Unrestrained and bold
奔放大胆
Radiantly blooming
绽放光彩
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Survival
生存
She's very serious on Tianping Island
她在天平岛很认真
Before I came, I was extremely passive
来之前我是极其被动的
I only notice people who like me
我只注意到喜欢我的人
I just don’t take the initiative myself
我只是自己不主动
to approach someone
接近某人
or actively get to know someone
或主动去认识某人
But seeing the stories around me
但看到身边的故事
it’s true—the brave ones find love first
这是真的——勇敢的人首先找到爱情
So I think
所以我认为
I might, in the future, in relationships
我可能在未来的人际关系中
Fu Jie's Love Report from Tianping Island
付洁天平岛爱情报道
On Tianping Island
位于天平岛上
Your most frequent haunt is the fitness area
您最常去的地方是健身区
No doubt these benches
毫无疑问这些长凳
have witnessed your romantic encounters
见证了你们的浪漫邂逅
In the scales of preference
在偏好范围内
You've cast your favor towards
你已向
seven different girls
七个不同的女孩
May your heart in these turbulent waters
愿你的心在这汹涌的水中
finally find its harbor
终于找到了它的港湾
"Player"
“玩家”
Seven
七
Meanwhile, you've received affection from twenty-two
与此同时，你已经收到了二十二个人的喜爱
Outperforming 96.1% of male peers
表现优于 96.1% 的男性同龄人
The way to exude charm
散发魅力的方式
Can you teach us how?
你能教我们怎么做吗？
Fu Jie, the highly anticipated "double-door" contestant
万众期待的“双门”选手付洁
According to incomplete statistics
据不完全统计
Your game win rate
您的游戏胜率
In the final island departure dating game
在最后的离岛约会游戏中
Thanks to opponents going easy and teammates performing well
感谢对手的轻松和队友的出色表现
You coasted to victory
你轻松走向胜利
Three chances to leave the island
三次离岛机会
You only left once
你只离开过一次
Is the person you want to hold hands with now her?
你现在最想牵手的人是她吗？
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Please check your Tianping Island keywords
请检查您的天平岛关键字
That's right
这是正确的
Showstopper
搅局者
Steal the show
抢尽风头
This keyword
这个关键词
I think this
我认为这个
might get quite a lot of criticism
可能会受到很多批评
But at first, my heart
但一开始我的心
was not deeply moved.
并没有被深深感动。
On this island,
在这个岛上，
there was even a time
甚至有一段时间
when I really wanted to escape this environment.
当我真的很想逃离这个环境的时候。
Then I truly hoped
然后我真心希望
that every person I had the chance to meet
我有机会见到的每个人
and get to know,
并了解，
all of you who are so outstanding,
你们所有如此优秀的人，
would have more opportunities to stay on this island.
会有更多的机会留在这个岛上。
So, I
所以，我
basically, whoever I got to know and understand,
基本上，无论我认识和理解谁，
I would vote for them.
我会投票给他们。
It wasn’t until the final moments
直到最后时刻
that my heart gradually calmed down.
我的心渐渐平静下来。
Only then did I realize that I truly liked it here.
这时我才发现我真的很喜欢这里。
I began to integrate with everyone.
我开始和大家融为一体。
In short, it was a very unforgettable experience.
总之，这是一次非常难忘的经历。
And I also accept the points that people criticized about me.
我也接受人们对我的批评。
No matter what,
无论，
How could I possibly regret it at this point?
事已至此，我怎么可能后悔呢？
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Our Brother Tao Zhi
我们的陶志弟兄
His expression is so adorable
他的表情太可爱了
Tao Zhi's Love Report from Balance Island
平衡岛陶智的爱情报告
Hello, Tao Zhi
Hello, Tao Zhi
On your first day on the island
上岛第一天
You were drawn to a touch of green
你被一抹绿色所吸引
You gave all your weights to the same person
你把所有的重量都给了同一个人
Do you still remember how you felt when making that choice?
你还记得当时做出这个选择时的感受吗？
You are the only islander
你是唯一的岛民
who left midway but returned to Balance Island
中途离开却又回到了平衡岛
Your sincerity and longing moved everyone
你的真诚和渴望感动了所有人
When you returned to Balance Island again
当你再次回到平衡岛时
This became your highlight moment on the island
这成为您在岛上的亮点时刻
Dating is something that brings joy
约会是一件能带来快乐的事情
But for you, perhaps it's a bit...
但对于你来说，或许有点……
You've won island dating privileges twice in total
您总共获得两次岛屿约会特权
Accidentally dated three girls on the island
意外地在岛上约会了三个女孩
Your film camera captured
你的胶片相机捕捉到的
many of Tianping Island's most beautiful moments
天平岛许多最美的瞬间
Etching memories into the fabric of time
将记忆铭刻在时间的结构中
May every photo you see in the future
愿你以后看到的每一张照片
be like opening wonderful surprise blind boxes
就像打开奇妙的惊喜盲盒
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Here are your Tianping Island keywords
这是您的天平岛关键词
Sincerity
诚意
Then I'll be going
那我就去
Chen Meng'er's Tianping Island Love Report
陈梦儿的天平岛爱情报告
She's so adorable
她是如此可爱
Hello, Chen Meng'er
陈梦儿你好
April 2, 2024
2024 年 4 月 2 日
Water sports were always your forte
水上运动一直是你的强项
But it seems
但看来
Daniel enjoyed them even more than you
丹尼尔比你更喜欢它们
During those eight days on the island
在岛上的这八天里
You put your all into everything you did
你为所做的一切付出了全部
The bread was delicious
面包很好吃
Others chat nonstop during dates
其他人在约会期间聊天不停
Your dates focus on eating first
你的约会重点是先吃饭
I really admire that about you
我真的很佩服你这一点
Only "Eating Champion" Guo Xu
唯有“吃冠军”郭旭
could rival you in this
在这方面可以与你竞争
Good reminder
好提醒
Okay
好的
Your Tianping Island keywords
您的天平岛关键词
Awesome
惊人的
Now I remember a song lyric
现在我想起了一首歌词
Thank you
谢谢
Chen Mengjia's Love Report from Tianping Island
陈梦佳的天平岛爱情报告
Hello, Chen Mengjia
Hello, Chen Mengjia
On Tianping Island
位于天平岛上
Every day's journey was accompanied by your tears
每天的旅途都有你的泪水陪伴
Congratulations on earning the title "Little Crybaby"
恭喜您获得“小爱哭鬼”称号
Even so
即便如此
You remain the hibiscus flower blooming
你依然是盛开的芙蓉花
on this tropical island
在这个热带岛屿上
Perhaps this trip to Tianping Island
也许这次天平岛之旅
left some regrets in your heart
心里留下一些遗憾
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Candid
坦率
Please check your Tianping Island keywords
请检查您的天平岛关键字
Little sun
小太阳
Everyone cried
大家都哭了
Gu Zhenxiang's Love Report on Tianping Island
Gu Zhenxiang's Love Report on Tianping Island
Hello, Gu Zhenxiang
Hello, Gu Zhenxiang
Upon first arriving on the island
第一次到达岛上时
The meeting of the three
三人的会面
But in relationships, it's hard to determine who came first
但在人际关系中，很难确定谁先谁后
As someone with "indecision syndrome"
作为一个患有“犹豫不决综合症”的人
Making choices
做出选择
has probably caused you some distress
可能给你带来了一些困扰
Winning the first off-island date privilege
赢得首次离岛约会特权
led you to an awkward date situation
让你陷入尴尬的约会局面
After returning, facing her again with your feelings unrequited
回来后再次面对她，单恋
Apologizing clumsily
笨拙地道歉
I really owe Chen Mengjia an apology
真欠陈梦佳一个道歉
I'm sorry
对不起
I'm truly sorry
我真的很抱歉
Accompanying her cautiously
小心翼翼地陪伴着她
You've been trying hard to make amends
你一直在努力弥补
Those happy moments getting beaten at pool
那些在泳池​​里被打败的幸福时刻
Was it like this?
是这样的吗？
Sweat and smiles at the ends of the earth
汗水和微笑在天涯海角
I wonder if your efforts
我想知道你的努力是否
received the response you hoped for
收到了您希望的答复
Friendship and love
友情与爱情
Have you learned this lesson?
你学到这个教训了吗？
When the time comes, ask your heart again
到时候再问问自己的心
If it's become more certain
如果变得更加确定
Your Tianping Island spirit
你的天平岛精神
Indecisiveness
优柔寡断
Here's your Tianping Island keyword
这是您的天平岛关键字
Inner conflict
内心冲突
Actually quite similar to Gu Zhenxiang
Actually quite similar to Gu Zhenxiang
I think it's really well written
我觉得写得真的很好
It captures most of my thoughts
它捕捉了我大部分的想法
I still feel I'm not very mature
我还是觉得自己不太成熟
Many things happened to me these twelve days
这十二天里我发生了很多事情
New thoughts every day
每天都有新想法
Changing three times daily
每日更换3次
Everyone goes through this
每个人都会经历这个
Right
正确的
And especially
尤其是
Regarding the Chen Mengjia situation
Regarding the Chen Mengjia situation
I was definitely in the wrong
我绝对是错的
That's absolutely true
这绝对是真的
So I think
所以我认为
This was something I needed to experience
这是我需要经历的事情
I see it as growth
我将其视为成长
It will help me improve
它将帮助我进步
At least you finally kept your promise to her
至少你终于兑现了对她的承诺
I got completely crushed yesterday
昨天我彻底崩溃了
Okay
好的
It's all in the past
一切都已成为过去
I'll miss this place
我会想念这个地方
I'll miss this restaurant
我会想念这家餐厅的
Yes, me too
是的，我也是
It witnessed my love
它见证了我的爱情
Let's shout something, okay?
我们喊点什么吧，好吗？
Okay
好的
I said
我说
Goodbye
再见
I want to come again
我想再来一次
Let's come together
让我们一起来吧
I want to come to Hainan
我想去海南
I'm going to change clothes.
我去换衣服。
Let's eat.
我们吃饭吧。
Gotta change clothes before eating.
吃饭前一定要换衣服。
Meal buddies.
饭友们。
Have you eaten?
你吃过了吗？
Not yet, eating now.
还没，正在吃。
Let's eat.
我们吃饭吧。
Probably the last meal in this place.
可能是在这个地方的最后一顿饭。
Feeling really mixed.
心情真是五味杂陈。
This journey for me...
这次旅行对我来说...
It's painful and complicated.
这是痛苦且复杂的。
Same for me.
对我来说也一样。
Thanks, Zheng Dedong.
Thanks, Zheng Dedong.
Without you, today wouldn't exist.
没有你，就没有今天。
You two being happy is what matters most.
你们两个开心最重要。
It's amazing.
太棒了。
When you say "leave me behind,"
当你说“把我抛在身后”时
I can't stand it.
我受不了了。
I can't take it anymore
我再也受不了了
Let me get you some tissue
让我给你拿点纸巾
This situation is really tough
这种情况确实很艰难
First time seeing Zheng Dedong cry
第一次见郑德东哭
I just can't handle this
我就是无法处理这个
This kind of brotherly bond gets me every time
这种兄弟情谊每次都让我感动
This brotherly affection is what gets me most
这种兄弟情最让我感动
We're all good brothers here
我们这里都是好兄弟
Whenever I feel
每当我感觉
That I still have this kind of brotherhood in my life
我的生活中仍然有这种兄弟情谊
I get really emotional
我真的很激动
To be honest
说实话
I believe relationships between people
我相信人与人之间的关系
Are about sincerity exchanged for sincerity
都是用真心换真心
And our minds are aligned
我们的思想是一致的
Our personalities complement each other
我们的性格互补
What do you call it
你叫它什么
We're on the same wavelength
我们处于同一波长
Completely in sync
完全同步
Zheng Dedong is an amazing young man
Zheng Dedong is an amazing young man
He's actually extremely sensitive inside
他其实内心极其敏感
But he's not good at expressing himself
但他不善于表达自己
Yet being with him makes you feel secure
但和他在一起会让你有安全感
In today's society
在当今社会
It's really hard to find
真的很难找
Such genuine friends
如此真诚的朋友
Truly
确实
Today is the last day on the island.
今天是在岛上的最后一天。
Have you made up your mind?
你下定决心了吗？
The clock district is now open.
时钟区现已开放。
All islanders may proceed there at your own pace.
所有岛民都可以按照自己的节奏前往那里。
I'll go.
我去吧。
Make your own...
自己做...
...decision about whether to confess or invite someone.
...关于是否坦白或邀请某人的决定。
Jiang Shangru has lost his soul.
姜尚如失去了灵魂。
Awaiting good news.
等待好消息。
Dear islanders, hello
亲爱的岛民们，你们好
Today is the last day
今天是最后一天
of your adventure on Tianping Island
天平岛冒险之旅
Have you made up your mind?
你下定决心了吗？
Confession invitation cards
告白邀请卡
have been prepared for you
已经为你准备好了
If you already have an answer in your heart
如果你心里已经有了答案
then pick up the pen and write their name
然后拿起笔写下他们的名字
Writing the name means
写下名字的意思是
you're inviting them for the next session
您邀请他们参加下一次会议
Mutual selection counts as the boy inviting the girl
互选算男孩邀请女孩
If you choose to give up on confessing
如果你选择放弃表白
please close the box
请关闭盒子
and return to the tent area
并返回帐篷区
On this final day at Tianping Island
在天平岛的最后一天
who has captured your heart?
谁俘获了你的心？
I will definitely choose Jiang Shangru
我一定会选择姜尚儒
Okay
好的
Jiang Shangru will definitely choose me
姜尚如一定会选择我
Otherwise he would have consistently chosen me all along
不然他会一直选择我
Why
为什么
It's a pleasure to meet you.
很高兴认识你。
Many things
很多事情
aren't really needed
并不真正需要
I don't need to elaborate further
我不需要进一步阐述
because she understands
因为她明白
So just a few simple words
所以只需要简单的几句话
to convey the meaning is enough
传达意思就足够了
Write it here
写在这里
Okay
好的